<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Populars on Get Recipes site</title>
    <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/popular/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Populars on Get Recipes site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 15:44:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/popular/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Healthy Egg Benedict</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/16-recipe-of-ultimate-healthy-egg-benedict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 15:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/16-recipe-of-ultimate-healthy-egg-benedict/</guid>
      <description>Healthy Egg Benedict
Hey everyone, it is Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, healthy egg benedict. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Healthy Egg Benedict is one of the most favored of recent trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions daily. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it is quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Quick Quick and Easy Lasagna</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/44-recipe-of-quick-quick-and-easy-lasagna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 14:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/44-recipe-of-quick-quick-and-easy-lasagna/</guid>
      <description>Quick and Easy Lasagna
Hello everybody, it is Drew, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, quick and easy lasagna. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Quick and Easy Lasagna is one of the most popular of recent trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Ultimate Caesar Salad with a twist</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/36-simple-way-to-make-ultimate-caesar-salad-with-a-twist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 03:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/36-simple-way-to-make-ultimate-caesar-salad-with-a-twist/</guid>
      <description>Caesar Salad with a twist
Hey everyone, it is Jim, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, caesar salad with a twist. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Caesar Salad with a twist is one of the most well liked of recent trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week My Christmas Stuffing 💖</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/29-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-my-christmas-stuffing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 09:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/29-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-my-christmas-stuffing/</guid>
      <description>My Christmas Stuffing 💖
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, my christmas stuffing 💖. It is one of my favorites. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
My Christmas Stuffing 💖 is one of the most popular of recent trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it is fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Apple Cider Turkey</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/1-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-apple-cider-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 18:41:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/1-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-apple-cider-turkey/</guid>
      <description>Apple Cider Turkey
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, apple cider turkey. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Tell mama no more dried out Turkey for your holiday dinner anymore. Watch step by step how to make an Apple Cider brine and then slow roast a Turkey on the.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Easy Ravioli Lasagna Bake</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/46-how-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-easy-ravioli-lasagna-bake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 09:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/46-how-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-easy-ravioli-lasagna-bake/</guid>
      <description>Easy Ravioli Lasagna Bake
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, easy ravioli lasagna bake. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Easy Ravioli Lasagna Bake is one of the most favored of current trending foods on earth. It is enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Quick and Easy Lasagna</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/43-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-quick-and-easy-lasagna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 06:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/43-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-quick-and-easy-lasagna/</guid>
      <description>Quick and Easy Lasagna
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, quick and easy lasagna. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Quick and Easy Lasagna is one of the most favored of recent trending foods in the world. It is simple, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Quick Easy Lasagna Rolls Up</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/39-how-to-prepare-quick-easy-lasagna-rolls-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/39-how-to-prepare-quick-easy-lasagna-rolls-up/</guid>
      <description>Easy Lasagna Rolls Up
Hey everyone, it is me again, Dan, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, easy lasagna rolls up. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Easy Lasagna Rolls Up is one of the most well liked of current trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Christmas Turkey Crown With Clementines &amp;amp;amp; Rosemary</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/18-how-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-christmas-turkey-crown-with-clementines-and-amp-rosemary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 17:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/18-how-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-christmas-turkey-crown-with-clementines-and-amp-rosemary/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Turkey Crown With Clementines &amp;amp;amp; Rosemary
Hey everyone, it is John, welcome to our recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, christmas turkey crown with clementines &amp;amp; rosemary. One of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Christmas Turkey Crown With Clementines &amp;amp; Rosemary is one of the most popular of current trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Any-night-of-the-week Simple Lasagna</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/48-how-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-simple-lasagna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/48-how-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-simple-lasagna/</guid>
      <description>Simple Lasagna
Hello everybody, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, simple lasagna. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Simple Lasagna is one of the most well liked of current trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily. It is easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Ultimate Apple Cider Turkey</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/2-simple-way-to-prepare-ultimate-apple-cider-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/2-simple-way-to-prepare-ultimate-apple-cider-turkey/</guid>
      <description>Apple Cider Turkey
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, apple cider turkey. One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Apple Cider Turkey is one of the most favored of current trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes yummy. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily. They are nice and they look fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Speedy Homemade Easy Minced Beef Lasagna</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/38-easiest-way-to-make-speedy-homemade-easy-minced-beef-lasagna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 01:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/38-easiest-way-to-make-speedy-homemade-easy-minced-beef-lasagna/</guid>
      <description>Homemade Easy Minced Beef Lasagna
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, homemade easy minced beef lasagna. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Homemade Easy Minced Beef Lasagna is one of the most popular of recent trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Homemade Simple Lasagna</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/47-step-by-step-guide-to-make-homemade-simple-lasagna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 20:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/47-step-by-step-guide-to-make-homemade-simple-lasagna/</guid>
      <description>Simple Lasagna
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, simple lasagna. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Simple Lasagna is one of the most favored of recent trending foods on earth. It is easy, it is quick, it tastes yummy. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Speedy Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sandwich</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/31-recipe-of-speedy-vickys-christmas-leftovers-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 06:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/31-recipe-of-speedy-vickys-christmas-leftovers-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sandwich
Hello everybody, it is Drew, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, vickys christmas leftovers sandwich. One of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sandwich is one of the most well liked of current trending foods on earth. It is easy, it is quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Quick Bone Broth</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/17-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-quick-bone-broth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/17-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-quick-bone-broth/</guid>
      <description>Bone Broth
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, bone broth. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Bone Broth is one of the most popular of current trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes yummy. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Favorite Closer to Christmas,                     TURKEY CHOILA</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/23-recipe-of-favorite-closer-to-christmas-turkey-choila/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/23-recipe-of-favorite-closer-to-christmas-turkey-choila/</guid>
      <description>Closer to Christmas, TURKEY CHOILA
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, closer to christmas, turkey choila. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Closer to Christmas, TURKEY CHOILA is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Quick Easy Peesy yet Absolutely Delicious-y Lasagna!</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/42-step-by-step-guide-to-make-quick-easy-peesy-yet-absolutely-delicious-y-lasagna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 19:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/42-step-by-step-guide-to-make-quick-easy-peesy-yet-absolutely-delicious-y-lasagna/</guid>
      <description>Easy Peesy yet Absolutely Delicious-y Lasagna!
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Dave, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, easy peesy yet absolutely delicious-y lasagna!. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Easy Peesy yet Absolutely Delicious-y Lasagna! is one of the most popular of recent trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Homemade Perfect Christmas Turkey</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/3-how-to-prepare-homemade-perfect-christmas-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/3-how-to-prepare-homemade-perfect-christmas-turkey/</guid>
      <description>Perfect Christmas Turkey
Hey everyone, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, perfect christmas turkey. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Perfect Christmas Turkey is one of the most popular of current trending meals in the world. It is simple, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Award-winning My Christmas Turkey</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/22-simple-way-to-make-award-winning-my-christmas-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 07:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/22-simple-way-to-make-award-winning-my-christmas-turkey/</guid>
      <description>My Christmas Turkey
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, my christmas turkey. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
My Christmas Turkey is one of the most popular of current trending foods in the world. It is easy, it is quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Favorite 3 way Xmas leftovers sandwich</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/35-recipe-of-favorite-3-way-xmas-leftovers-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 18:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/35-recipe-of-favorite-3-way-xmas-leftovers-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>3 way Xmas leftovers sandwich
Hey everyone, it is Louise, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, 3 way xmas leftovers sandwich. One of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
3 way Xmas leftovers sandwich is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Favorite Christmas turkey arroz caldo</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/0-easiest-way-to-prepare-favorite-christmas-turkey-arroz-caldo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 04:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/0-easiest-way-to-prepare-favorite-christmas-turkey-arroz-caldo/</guid>
      <description>Christmas turkey arroz caldo
Hey everyone, it is Drew, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, christmas turkey arroz caldo. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Christmas turkey arroz caldo is one of the most favored of current trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Any-night-of-the-week Turkey Chorizo, Cauliflower Rice, and Etc</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/6-how-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-turkey-chorizo-cauliflower-rice-and-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/6-how-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-turkey-chorizo-cauliflower-rice-and-etc/</guid>
      <description>Turkey Chorizo, Cauliflower Rice, and Etc
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, turkey chorizo, cauliflower rice, and etc. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Turkey Chorizo, Cauliflower Rice, and Etc is one of the most popular of recent trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Favorite Mandys Christmas Turkey and ham leftover sambo</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/25-simple-way-to-prepare-favorite-mandys-christmas-turkey-and-ham-leftover-sambo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/25-simple-way-to-prepare-favorite-mandys-christmas-turkey-and-ham-leftover-sambo/</guid>
      <description>Mandys Christmas Turkey and ham leftover sambo
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Jim, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, mandys christmas turkey and ham leftover sambo. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Mandys Christmas Turkey and ham leftover sambo is one of the most favored of current trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Speedy Applewood Smoked Turkey Breast</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/8-step-by-step-guide-to-make-speedy-applewood-smoked-turkey-breast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 12:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/8-step-by-step-guide-to-make-speedy-applewood-smoked-turkey-breast/</guid>
      <description>Applewood Smoked Turkey Breast
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, applewood smoked turkey breast. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Applewood Smoked Turkey Breast is one of the most popular of recent trending foods in the world. It is simple, it is quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Homemade Slow-cooker Loose Meat Sandwiches</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/37-recipe-of-homemade-slow-cooker-loose-meat-sandwiches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 06:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/37-recipe-of-homemade-slow-cooker-loose-meat-sandwiches/</guid>
      <description>Slow-cooker Loose Meat Sandwiches
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, slow-cooker loose meat sandwiches. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Slow-cooker Loose Meat Sandwiches is one of the most well liked of current trending foods in the world. It is simple, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Super Quick Homemade Turkey Choila (Typical Nepalese Grill &amp;amp;amp; Marinated Meat Snacks)  Christmas in Nepalese way</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/27-simple-way-to-make-super-quick-homemade-turkey-choila-typical-nepalese-grill-and-amp-marinated-meat-snacks-christmas-in-nepalese-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 09:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/27-simple-way-to-make-super-quick-homemade-turkey-choila-typical-nepalese-grill-and-amp-marinated-meat-snacks-christmas-in-nepalese-way/</guid>
      <description>Turkey Choila (Typical Nepalese Grill &amp;amp;amp; Marinated Meat Snacks) Christmas in Nepalese way
Hey everyone, it is John, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, turkey choila (typical nepalese grill &amp;amp; marinated meat snacks) christmas in nepalese way. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Turkey Choila (Typical Nepalese Grill &amp;amp; Marinated Meat Snacks) Christmas in Nepalese way is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Favorite Leftover christmas turkey curry</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/21-recipe-of-favorite-leftover-christmas-turkey-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 04:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/21-recipe-of-favorite-leftover-christmas-turkey-curry/</guid>
      <description>Leftover christmas turkey curry
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, leftover christmas turkey curry. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Leftover christmas turkey curry is one of the most favored of recent trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Speedy Santa Fe Stuffed Peppers</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/11-easiest-way-to-prepare-speedy-santa-fe-stuffed-peppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 13:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/11-easiest-way-to-prepare-speedy-santa-fe-stuffed-peppers/</guid>
      <description>Santa Fe Stuffed Peppers
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, santa fe stuffed peppers. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Santa Fe Stuffed Peppers is one of the most well liked of recent trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Perfect Vickys Maple Roast Christmas Turkey, GF DF EF SF NF</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/26-easiest-way-to-make-perfect-vickys-maple-roast-christmas-turkey-gf-df-ef-sf-nf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 08:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/26-easiest-way-to-make-perfect-vickys-maple-roast-christmas-turkey-gf-df-ef-sf-nf/</guid>
      <description>Vickys Maple Roast Christmas Turkey, GF DF EF SF NF
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Dave, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, vickys maple roast christmas turkey, gf df ef sf nf. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Vickys Maple Roast Christmas Turkey, GF DF EF SF NF is one of the most favored of recent trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Dishlycious Tamale Pie</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/10-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-dishlycious-tamale-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 16:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/10-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-dishlycious-tamale-pie/</guid>
      <description>Dishlycious Tamale Pie
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, dishlycious tamale pie. One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Dishlycious Tamale Pie is one of the most favored of recent trending foods on earth. It is appreciated by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Homemade Gordon Ramsey, s Christmas Turkey. #ChristmasGift#Mainmeal</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/20-step-by-step-guide-to-make-homemade-gordon-ramsey-s-christmas-turkey-christmasgiftmainmeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 23:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/20-step-by-step-guide-to-make-homemade-gordon-ramsey-s-christmas-turkey-christmasgiftmainmeal/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Ramsey, s Christmas Turkey. #ChristmasGift#Mainmeal
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, gordon ramsey, s christmas turkey. #christmasgift#mainmeal. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Gordon Ramsey, s Christmas Turkey. #ChristmasGift#Mainmeal is one of the most popular of recent trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Quick Gordon Ramsay&amp;amp;#39;s Christmas Turkey</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/24-recipe-of-quick-gordon-ramsay-and-39-s-christmas-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/24-recipe-of-quick-gordon-ramsay-and-39-s-christmas-turkey/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Ramsay&amp;#39;s Christmas Turkey
Hello everybody, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, gordon ramsay&#39;s christmas turkey. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Gordon Ramsay&#39;s Christmas Turkey is one of the most favored of current trending foods in the world. It is enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Christmas grilled turkey and cheese</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/5-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-christmas-grilled-turkey-and-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 22:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/5-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-christmas-grilled-turkey-and-cheese/</guid>
      <description>Christmas grilled turkey and cheese
Hey everyone, it is Brad, welcome to our recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, christmas grilled turkey and cheese. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Christmas grilled turkey and cheese is one of the most favored of recent trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Homemade Christmas Bird</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/33-recipe-of-homemade-christmas-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 05:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/33-recipe-of-homemade-christmas-bird/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Bird
Hello everybody, it is Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, christmas bird. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Christmas Bird is one of the most favored of recent trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it is fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Quick Easy Ravioli Lasagna Bake</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/45-easiest-way-to-prepare-quick-easy-ravioli-lasagna-bake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 16:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/45-easiest-way-to-prepare-quick-easy-ravioli-lasagna-bake/</guid>
      <description>Easy Ravioli Lasagna Bake
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, easy ravioli lasagna bake. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Easy Ravioli Lasagna Bake is one of the most popular of recent trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Speedy Collard greens</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/14-simple-way-to-prepare-speedy-collard-greens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 13:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/14-simple-way-to-prepare-speedy-collard-greens/</guid>
      <description>Collard greens
Hey everyone, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, collard greens. One of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Collard greens is one of the most popular of current trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes delicious. It is enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Homemade My Christmas Stuffing to go with Turkey #Sidedish#ChristmasGift</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/19-simple-way-to-prepare-homemade-my-christmas-stuffing-to-go-with-turkey-sidedishchristmasgift/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 11:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/19-simple-way-to-prepare-homemade-my-christmas-stuffing-to-go-with-turkey-sidedishchristmasgift/</guid>
      <description>My Christmas Stuffing to go with Turkey #Sidedish#ChristmasGift
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, my christmas stuffing to go with turkey #sidedish#christmasgift. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
My Christmas Stuffing to go with Turkey #Sidedish#ChristmasGift is one of the most well liked of current trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Perfect Christmas canapes</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/34-steps-to-prepare-perfect-christmas-canapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 06:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/34-steps-to-prepare-perfect-christmas-canapes/</guid>
      <description>Christmas canapes
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, christmas canapes. It is one of my favorites. This time, I will make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Christmas canapes is one of the most favored of recent trending meals on earth. It is enjoyed by millions every day. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Beany Sloppy Joe Casserole</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/13-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-beany-sloppy-joe-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 23:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/13-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-beany-sloppy-joe-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Beany Sloppy Joe Casserole
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Louise, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, beany sloppy joe casserole. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Beany Sloppy Joe Casserole is one of the most well liked of current trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Mandys Christmas soup</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/32-recipe-of-ultimate-mandys-christmas-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 02:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/32-recipe-of-ultimate-mandys-christmas-soup/</guid>
      <description>Mandys Christmas soup
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, mandys christmas soup. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Mandys Christmas soup is one of the most favored of recent trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it is fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Christmas roll</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/28-recipe-of-perfect-christmas-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 18:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/28-recipe-of-perfect-christmas-roll/</guid>
      <description>Christmas roll
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, christmas roll. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Christmas roll is one of the most favored of recent trending meals on earth. It is easy, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes delicious. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sausage Rolls, GF DF EF SF NF</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/30-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-vickys-christmas-leftovers-sausage-rolls-gf-df-ef-sf-nf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/30-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-vickys-christmas-leftovers-sausage-rolls-gf-df-ef-sf-nf/</guid>
      <description>Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sausage Rolls, GF DF EF SF NF
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, vickys christmas leftovers sausage rolls, gf df ef sf nf. It is one of my favorites. This time, I will make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sausage Rolls, GF DF EF SF NF is one of the most popular of recent trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Homemade Dean&amp;amp;#39;s Crunchy Santa Fe Turkey Deli Sandwich</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/4-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-homemade-dean-and-39-s-crunchy-santa-fe-turkey-deli-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 20:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/4-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-homemade-dean-and-39-s-crunchy-santa-fe-turkey-deli-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>Dean&amp;#39;s Crunchy Santa Fe Turkey Deli Sandwich
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, dean&#39;s crunchy santa fe turkey deli sandwich. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Dean&#39;s Crunchy Santa Fe Turkey Deli Sandwich is one of the most favored of current trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Easy Peesy yet Absolutely Delicious-y Lasagna!</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/41-how-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-easy-peesy-yet-absolutely-delicious-y-lasagna/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 02:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/41-how-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-easy-peesy-yet-absolutely-delicious-y-lasagna/</guid>
      <description>Easy Peesy yet Absolutely Delicious-y Lasagna!
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Dave, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, easy peesy yet absolutely delicious-y lasagna!. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Easy Peesy yet Absolutely Delicious-y Lasagna! is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Favorite Easy Zucchini Lasagna</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/40-recipe-of-favorite-easy-zucchini-lasagna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/40-recipe-of-favorite-easy-zucchini-lasagna/</guid>
      <description>Easy Zucchini Lasagna
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, easy zucchini lasagna. One of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Easy Zucchini Lasagna is one of the most popular of current trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Quick Copycat Skyline Chili</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/12-recipe-of-quick-copycat-skyline-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 15:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/12-recipe-of-quick-copycat-skyline-chili/</guid>
      <description>Copycat Skyline Chili
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, copycat skyline chili. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Copycat Skyline Chili is one of the most well liked of current trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Homemade Broccoli Salad</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/15-easiest-way-to-prepare-homemade-broccoli-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 14:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/15-easiest-way-to-prepare-homemade-broccoli-salad/</guid>
      <description>Broccoli Salad
Hey everyone, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, broccoli salad. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Broccoli Salad is one of the most favored of current trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Bacon Turkey</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/9-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-bacon-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/9-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-bacon-turkey/</guid>
      <description>Bacon Turkey
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, bacon turkey. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Turkey bacon is a meat prepared from chopped, formed, cured, and smoked turkey, which is commonly marketed as a low-fat alternative to pork bacon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Speedy Tomatillo Braised Turkey Tacos</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/7-easiest-way-to-make-speedy-tomatillo-braised-turkey-tacos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/7-easiest-way-to-make-speedy-tomatillo-braised-turkey-tacos/</guid>
      <description>Tomatillo Braised Turkey Tacos
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Jim, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, tomatillo braised turkey tacos. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Tomatillo Braised Turkey Tacos is one of the most favored of recent trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
