<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>greens on Get Recipes site</title>
    <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/tags/greens/</link>
    <description>Recent content in greens on Get Recipes site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 17:42:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/tags/greens/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Tortilla Greens Chickpeas Salad Bowl with Refried Bean Dates dressing</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/113-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-tortilla-greens-chickpeas-salad-bowl-with-refried-bean-dates-dressing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 17:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/113-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-tortilla-greens-chickpeas-salad-bowl-with-refried-bean-dates-dressing/</guid>
      <description>Tortilla Greens Chickpeas Salad Bowl with Refried Bean Dates dressing
Hello everybody, it is Louise, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, tortilla greens chickpeas salad bowl with refried bean dates dressing. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Tortilla Greens Chickpeas Salad Bowl with Refried Bean Dates dressing is one of the most popular of current trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Tortilla Greens Chickpeas Salad Bowl with Refried Bean Dates dressing</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/114-recipe-of-perfect-tortilla-greens-chickpeas-salad-bowl-with-refried-bean-dates-dressing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 08:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/114-recipe-of-perfect-tortilla-greens-chickpeas-salad-bowl-with-refried-bean-dates-dressing/</guid>
      <description>Tortilla Greens Chickpeas Salad Bowl with Refried Bean Dates dressing
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, tortilla greens chickpeas salad bowl with refried bean dates dressing. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Tortilla Greens Chickpeas Salad Bowl with Refried Bean Dates dressing is one of the most well liked of current trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Speedy Collard greens</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/14-simple-way-to-prepare-speedy-collard-greens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 13:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/14-simple-way-to-prepare-speedy-collard-greens/</guid>
      <description>Collard greens
Hey everyone, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, collard greens. One of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Collard greens is one of the most popular of current trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes delicious. It is enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
