<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bacon on Get Recipes site</title>
    <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/tags/bacon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bacon on Get Recipes site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 01:32:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/tags/bacon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Bacon Pea Creamy Pasta Salad with lemon parmesan dressing</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/109-simple-way-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-bacon-pea-creamy-pasta-salad-with-lemon-parmesan-dressing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 01:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/109-simple-way-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-bacon-pea-creamy-pasta-salad-with-lemon-parmesan-dressing/</guid>
      <description>Bacon Pea Creamy Pasta Salad with lemon parmesan dressing
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, bacon pea creamy pasta salad with lemon parmesan dressing. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Bacon Pea Creamy Pasta Salad with lemon parmesan dressing is one of the most popular of recent trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Homemade Bacon Pea Creamy Pasta Salad with lemon parmesan dressing</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/110-simple-way-to-make-homemade-bacon-pea-creamy-pasta-salad-with-lemon-parmesan-dressing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 20:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/110-simple-way-to-make-homemade-bacon-pea-creamy-pasta-salad-with-lemon-parmesan-dressing/</guid>
      <description>Bacon Pea Creamy Pasta Salad with lemon parmesan dressing
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, bacon pea creamy pasta salad with lemon parmesan dressing. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Bacon Pea Creamy Pasta Salad with lemon parmesan dressing is one of the most favored of recent trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Favorite Bacon Ranch Cheesy Potatoes</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/68-recipe-of-favorite-bacon-ranch-cheesy-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 16:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/68-recipe-of-favorite-bacon-ranch-cheesy-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>Bacon Ranch Cheesy Potatoes
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, bacon ranch cheesy potatoes. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Bacon Ranch Cheesy Potatoes is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods on earth. It is enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Quick Bacon Ranch Cheesy Potatoes</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/67-easiest-way-to-prepare-quick-bacon-ranch-cheesy-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 09:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/67-easiest-way-to-prepare-quick-bacon-ranch-cheesy-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>Bacon Ranch Cheesy Potatoes
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Dave, welcome to our recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, bacon ranch cheesy potatoes. It is one of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Bacon Ranch Cheesy Potatoes is one of the most favored of recent trending foods in the world. It is easy, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Bacon Turkey</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/9-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-bacon-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/9-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-bacon-turkey/</guid>
      <description>Bacon Turkey
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, bacon turkey. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Turkey bacon is a meat prepared from chopped, formed, cured, and smoked turkey, which is commonly marketed as a low-fat alternative to pork bacon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
