<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vickys on Get Recipes site</title>
    <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/tags/vickys/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vickys on Get Recipes site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 06:25:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/tags/vickys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Speedy Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sandwich</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/31-recipe-of-speedy-vickys-christmas-leftovers-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 06:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/31-recipe-of-speedy-vickys-christmas-leftovers-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sandwich
Hello everybody, it is Drew, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, vickys christmas leftovers sandwich. One of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sandwich is one of the most well liked of current trending foods on earth. It is easy, it is quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Perfect Vickys Maple Roast Christmas Turkey, GF DF EF SF NF</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/26-easiest-way-to-make-perfect-vickys-maple-roast-christmas-turkey-gf-df-ef-sf-nf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 08:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/26-easiest-way-to-make-perfect-vickys-maple-roast-christmas-turkey-gf-df-ef-sf-nf/</guid>
      <description>Vickys Maple Roast Christmas Turkey, GF DF EF SF NF
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Dave, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, vickys maple roast christmas turkey, gf df ef sf nf. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Vickys Maple Roast Christmas Turkey, GF DF EF SF NF is one of the most favored of recent trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sausage Rolls, GF DF EF SF NF</title>
      <link>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/30-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-vickys-christmas-leftovers-sausage-rolls-gf-df-ef-sf-nf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geteasyrecipesideas.web.app/30-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-vickys-christmas-leftovers-sausage-rolls-gf-df-ef-sf-nf/</guid>
      <description>Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sausage Rolls, GF DF EF SF NF
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, vickys christmas leftovers sausage rolls, gf df ef sf nf. It is one of my favorites. This time, I will make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Vickys Christmas Leftovers Sausage Rolls, GF DF EF SF NF is one of the most popular of recent trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
